Guide to the Douglas Crase and Frank Polach Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Douglas Crase and Frank Polach papers
1896-2013
GEN MSS 1134
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
68
(82 boxes) + 5 art
Crase, Douglas
Polach, Frank
Barneby, Rupert C., 1911-
Ripley, Dwight
Scope and Contents
Writings, correspondence, photographs, research materials, artwork, and other papers by, to, or relating to Douglas Crase and Frank Polach. Also includes materials materials relating to Rupert Barnaby and Dwight Ripley.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Granary Books, Inc. on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund and the Martin Greenblatt Foundation Book Fund in American Literature, 2014.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Box 86 (film): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Douglas Crase and Frank Polach
Douglas Crase is an American poet and writer. His husband, Frank Polach, is a poet, gardener, and former University Librarian at Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey.
Dwight Ripley and Rupert Barneby
Dwight Ripley was an English artist and patron of the arts associated with the New York School and the Tibor de Nagy Gallery. His life partner was Rupert Barneby, an English botanist.
American literature -- 20th Century; Botanists -- Great Britain; Gardeners -- United States; Poets, American -- 20th Century; Drawings (visual works); Photographs; Barneby, Rupert C., 1911-; Dash, Robert; Polach, Frank; Ripley, Dwight; Tibor de Nagy Gallery
- Douglas Crase papers, Series I
  - Correspondence
    - Incoming
      - Aaron, Valerie (Watts), undated (Box 1)
      - Abbott, Ken, undated (Box 1)
      - Abrahamson, Joan, undated (Box 1)
      - Akeroyd, John, undated (Box 1)
      - Ali, Agha Shahid, undated (Box 1)
      - Allardt, Linda, undated (Box 1)
      - Allen, Bruce, undated (Box 1)
      - Allen, Francis, undated (Box 1)
      - Allen, Ralph, undated (Box 1)
      - Alloway, Lawrence, undated (Box 1)
      - Ammons, A.R, undated (Box 1)
      - Anderson, Alexandra, undated (Box 1)
      - Anderson, Bruce, undated (Box 1)
      - Anderson, William, undated (Box 1)
      - Angell, Bobbi, undated (Box 1)
      - Anonymous, 1967 (Box 1)
      - Anonymous, 1968 (Box 1)
      - Anonymous, 1969 (Box 1)
      - Anonymous, 1970 (Box 1)
      - Anonymous, 1972 (Box 1)
      - Anonymous, 1993 (Box 1)
      - Anonymous, 1994 (Box 1)
      - Anonymous, 2011 (Box 1)
      - Anson, Philip, undated (Box 1)
      - Archibald, Jim and Jenny, undated (Box 1)
      - Asekoff, Lou, undated (Box 1)
      - Arnot, Andrew, undated (Box 1)
      - Ash, John, undated (Box 1)
      - Ashberry, John, undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Augst, Thomas, undated (Box 1)
      - Baad, Ardis (Smith), undated (Box 1)
      - Bablitch, Martha (Virtue), undated (Box 1)
      - Bacha, Diane, undated (Box 1)
      - Baker, Carlos, undated (Box 1)
      - Baker, Willard, undated (Box 1)
      - Ball, Angela, undated (Box 1)
      - Banton, Frank, 2006 (Box 1)
      - Baran, Susan, undated (Box 1)
      - Barber, Charles, undated (Box 1)
      - Barkley, Theodore, undated (Box 1)
      - Barneby, Rupert, undated (Box 1)
      - Barnett, Pamela, undated (Box 1)
      - Beasley, June, undated (Box 1)
      - Becker, Susan (Koethe), undated (Box 1)
      - Beckman, Joshua, undated (Box 1)
      - Bell, Ian Spencer, undated (Box 1)
      - Bellow, Rachel Newton, undated (Box 1)
      - Benedikt, Michael, undated (Box 1)
      - Bennett, Millicent, undated (Box 1)
      - Benson, Elaine, undated (Box 1)
      - Berman, Paul, undated (Box 1)
      - Bernard, April, undated (Box 1)
      - Berridge, David, undated (Box 1)
      - Bervin, Jen, undated (Box 1)
      - Berzins, Mirdza, undated (Box 1)
      - Bibbins, Mark, undated (Box 1)
      - Black, Douglas, undated (Box 1)
      - Black, Star, undated (Box 1)
      - Blanchfield, Brian, undated (Box 1)
      - Bloom, Harold, undated (Box 1)
      - Booth, Philip, undated (Box 1)
      - Bornarth, Sylvia, undated (Box 1)
      - Bowden, Colin, undated (Box 1)
      - Bowles, Marlin, undated (Box 1)
      - Boyd, Jonathan, undated (Box 1)
      - Bradley, George, undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Bradstreet, Rick, undated; 3 folders (Box 1)
      - Brainard, Joe, undated (Box 1)
      - Breidenbach, Thomas, undated (Box 1)
      - Brennan, Pierce, undated (Box 1)
      - Brewster, Eliza, undated (Box 1)
      - Briccetti, Lee, undated (Box 1)
      - Bristol, Barbara, undated (Box 1)
      - Britton, Donald, 1980-1989 (Box 2)
      - Brooklyn College, 1982 (Box 2)
      - Brookner, Aaron, 2013 (Box 2)
      - Brown, Brice, undated (Box 2)
      - Brown, Eric, 1980-1999; 3 folders-I private (Box 2)
      - Brubaker, Russ, undated (Box 2)
      - Bruner, Jerome, undated (Box 2)
      - Buck, William, undated (Box 2)
      - Burgin, Richard, undated (Box 2)
      - Butterworth, Dale, undated (Box 2)
      - Byrne, Brian (Fordham U.), undated (Box 2)
      - Campion, Peter, undated (Box 2)
      - Carduff, Christopher, undated (Box 2)
      - Carey, Tom, undated (Box 2)
      - Carrillo, Carlos, undated (Box 2)
      - Castilglia, Chris, undated (Box 2)
      - Catania, undated (Box 2)
      - Chapko, Julie (Nelson) (Brown), undated (Box 2)
      - Cherwinski, Joseph, undated (Box 2)
      - Chu, Lynn, undated (Box 2)
      - Clark, Barbara, undated; 4 folders (Box 2)
      - Clark, Michiko, undated; 4 folders (Box 2)
      - Clark, Philip, undated (Box 2)
      - Clinton, Gary and Con Millinger, undated (Box 2)
      - Cohen, Gil and Paul Gervais, undated (Box 2)
      - Cohen, Joel, undated (Box 2)
      - Cohen, Marc, undated (Box 2)
      - Cole, Henri, undated (Box 2)
      - Cole, Marsha, undated (Box 2)
      - Collins, Rowland, undated (Box 2)
      - Collier, Michael, undated (Box 2)
      - Cooper, Dennis, undated (Box 2)
      - Cooper, Phyllis (Gainder), undated (Box 2)
      - Corbett, William, undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
      - Corman, Sid, undated (Box 2)
      - Corn, Alfred, undated (Box 2)
      - Costello, Bonnie, undated (Box 2)
      - Cox, Christopher, undated (Box 2)
      - Craig, Earl, undated (Box 2)
      - Crase (letters to parents), undated (Box 2)
      - Crase, Elizabeth "Minnie" (Ward), undated (Box 2)
      - Crase, Gertrude (Winchester), 1970-1982; 5 folders (Box 3)
      - Crase, Margaret - mother, undated (Box 3)
      - Crase Margaret Fuller (Walmsley), undated (Box 3)
      - Crase, Norman - father, undated (Box 3)
      - Crawford, Rob, undated (Box 3)
      - Cronon, William, undated (Box 3)
      - Cullum, Lynne (GE), undated (Box 3)
      - Cummings, Conrad, undated (Box 3)
      - Cunningham, Merce, undated (Box 3)
      - Da Costa, Damian, undated (Box 3)
      - Danforth, Ted, undated (Box 3)
      - Danielson, Michael, undated (Box 3)
      - Dash, Robert, 1973-2012; 4 folders (Box 3)
      - Davenport, Guy, undated (Box 3)
      - De Evia, Edgar - Ed White's Friend, undated (Box 3)
      - De Grazia, Diane, undated (Box 3)
      - Delatolas, Iannis, undated (Box 3)
      - De Leo, Hank - pen-and-ink for Doug and Frank, undated (Box 3)
      - Del Propost, Sam, undated (Box 3)
      - Democratic State Central Committee of Michigan, undated (Box 3)
      - Dennis, Carl, undated (Box 3)
      - Detroit Law Firms, undated (Box 3)
      - Diget, Dennis - cousin, undated (Box 3)
      - Diget, Jane (Walmsley) - aunt, undated (Box 3)
      - Diget, Patricia Denny - cousin David's 2d wife, undated (Box 3)
      - Diggory, Terence, undated (Box 3)
      - Di Liberti, John, undated (Box 3)
      - Disch, Thomas, undated (Box 4)
      - Dlugos, Tim, undated (Box 4)
      - Dolph, Anne, undated (Box 4)
      - Donald, Roger, undated (Box 4)
      - W.B. Doner (ad agency), undated (Box 4)
      - Donovan, Williams, undated (Box 4)
      - Draper, Robert, undated (Box 4)
      - Dubbeld, Diana (Diget), undated (Box 4)
      - Duberman, Martin, undated (Box 4)
      - Duffany, Brett, undated (Box 4)
      - Dunn, Anne, undated (Box 4)
      - Dupont, Jerome, undated (Box 4)
      - Durrett, Arlene, undated (Box 4)
      - Earl, Martin, undated (Box 4)
      - Edelman, Lee, undated (Box 4)
      - Edmonds, Elizabeth, undated (Box 4)
      - Effron, Jesse, undated (Box 4)
      - Effron, Walter, undated (Box 4)
      - Eichwald, Richard, undated (Box 4)
      - Ellis, Caroline, undated (Box 4)
      - Elmslie, undated (Box 4)
      - Epler, Barbara, undated (Box 4)
      - Epstein, Barbara, undated (Box 4)
      - Epstein, Jeff, undated (Box 4)
      - Ercoli, Justin - Great Nephew, undated (Box 4)
      - Ercoli, Kelly (McAlvey) - Niece, undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Errington, Shelly, undated (Box 4)
      - Evans, Rob, undated (Box 4)
      - Falkner, Emmet, undated (Box 4)
      - Faxon, Jack, undated (Box 4)
      - Fein, Cheri, undated (Box 4)
      - Feinstein, Otto, undated (Box 4)
      - Fenza, David, undated (Box 4)
      - Ferency, Zolton, undated (Box 4)
      - Flory, Millie, undated (Box 4)
      - Ford, George, undated (Box 4)
      - Ford, Harry, undated (Box 4)
      - Ford, Mark, undated (Box 4)
      - Foster, Carter, undated (Box 4)
      - Foye, Raymond, undated (Box 4)
      - Franca, Paulo Gustavo, undated (Box 4)
      - Frankenthaler, Helen, undated (Box 4)
      - Frates, Tony, undated (Box 4)
      - Freeman, Katharine, undated (Box 4)
      - Freilicher, Jane, undated (Box 4)
      - Freund, Gerald, undated (Box 4)
      - Friday, Phil, undated (Box 4)
      - Frishkorn, David and Jack Hellaby, undated (Box 4)
      - Fuchs, Greg, undated (Box 4)
      - Fuller, Bessie Mabel - Great Aunt, undated (Box 4)
      - Fuller, Margaret, undated; 2 folders-1 "estate of:" (Box 4)
      - Fulton, Alice and Hank de Leo, undated (Box 4)
      - Gaal, Stephen, undated (Box 4)
      - Galassi, Jonathan, undated (Box 4)
      - Gale Research Co., undated (Box 4)
      - Garcia, Ric, undated (Box 4)
      - Garrison, Deborah, undated (Box 4)
      - Gay, Joan, undated (Box 4)
      - Gay Liberation Front, undated (Box 4)
      - General Electric, undated (Box 4)
      - General Theological Seminary, undated (Box 4)
      - Genovese, Eugene, undated (Box 4)
      - Gezari, Janet, undated (Box 4)
      - Giard, Robert, undated (Box 4)
      - Gillette, Frank, undated (Box 4)
      - Gillis, Robert, undated (Box 4)
      - Gioia, Dana, undated (Box 4)
      - Gizzi, [Peter], undated (Box 4)
      - Glines, undated (Box 4)
      - Glykokokalos, Iannis and Pauline, undated (Box 4)
      - Glyyn, Michael, undated (Box 4)
      - Godfrey, John, undated (Box 4)
      - Goldbarth, Albert, undated (Box 4)
      - Golde, Morris, undated (Box 4)
      - Gomez Aguilera, Fernando, undated (Box 4)
      - Gooch, Brad, undated (Box 4)
      - Gorin, Andrew, undated (Box 4)
      - Gormly, Debbie, undated (Box 4)
      - Gottlieb, Robert, undated (Box 4)
      - Graham, Lewraine, undated (Box 4)
      - Greene, Mott, undated (Box 4)
      - Griffith, E.V., undated (Box 4)
      - Grimes, James, undated (Box 4)
      - Groff, David, undated (Box 4)
      - Groffsky, Maxine, undated (Box 4)
      - Gross, Kenneth, undated (Box 4)
      - Grumet, Robert, undated (Box 4)
      - Guggenheim, undated (Box 4)
      - Gutierrez, Ramon, undated (Box 4)
      - Haaren, Peter, undated (Box 4)
      - Haber, William, undated (Box 4)
      - Hadas, Rachel, undated (Box 4)
      - Hainley, Bruce, undated (Box 4)
      - Hall, Donald, undated (Box 4)
      - Halpern, Richard, undated (Box 4)
      - Halsey, Alan, undated (Box 4)
      - Hammond, Mac, undated (Box 5)
      - Handy, Cortlandt W. - Parker Handy Scholarship Donor, undated (Box 5)
      - Hansen, Philip, undated (Box 5)
      - Harrison, Jeffrey, undated (Box 5)
      - Hart, Adelaide, undated (Box 5)
      - Hartigan, Grace, undated (Box 5)
      - Hartley, Glen, undated (Box 5)
      - Hartley, Glen and Lynn Chu, undated (Box 5)
      - Harvard Law School, undated (Box 5)
      - Hastings, Katharine, undated (Box 5)
      - Hatlen, Burton, undated (Box 5)
      - Hayes, Richard, undated (Box 5)
      - Healy, Tom, undated (Box 5)
      - Hearne, Vicki, undated (Box 5)
      - Hecht [Anthony], undated (Box 5)
      - Heiniger, Dale, undated (Box 5)
      - Heintzelman, Donald, undated (Box 5)
      - Hemingway, Mary, undated (Box 5)
      - Henderson, Bill, undated (Box 5)
      - Henry, DeWitt, undated (Box 5)
      - Henery, Gerrit, undated (Box 6)
      - Hill, Eugene, undated (Box 6)
      - Hilton, Charlotte (Fuller), undated (Box 6)
      - Hine, Daryl, undated (Box 6)
      - Hinton, Beverly, undated (Box 6)
      - Hirsch, Edward, undated (Box 6)
      - Hirsch, Faye, undated (Box 6)
      - Hobhouse, Penelope, undated (Box 6)
      - Hoff, Michael, undated (Box 6)
      - Hoffman, Daniel, undated (Box 6)
      - Hollander, John, undated (Box 6)
        Scope and Contents
        Including A Garland for John Hollander: October 28, 1989, assembled by Natalie Charkow and J.D. McClatchy. With a poem by Douglas.
      - Holman, Bob, undated (Box 6)
      - Holmes, Donald, undated (Box 6)
      - Holmes Articles, undated (Box 6)
      - Holmgren, Patricia, undated (Box 6)
      - Hood, Kimba (McAlvey), undated (Box 6)
      - Hoot, Scoot, undated (Box 6)
      - Hooten, Peter, undated (Box 6)
      - Hoover, Paul, undated (Box 6)
      - Hope, Ken, undated (Box 6)
      - Hopkins, Jeanette, undated (Box 6)
      - Hough, Linda (Eddy), undated (Box 6)
      - Howard, Richard, undated (Box 6)
      - Howe, Susan, undated; 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Howell, Anthony, undated (Box 6)
      - Huber J. Parker, undated (Box 6)
      - Hughes, Andy, undated (Box 6)
      - Hughes, Brigid, undated (Box 6)
      - Hughes, Robert, undated (Box 6)
      - Hulter, Marilyn (Nelson)(Crase), undated; 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Huxtable, Ada Louise, undated (Box 6)
      - Hyde, Lewis, undated (Box 6)
      - Ingham, Robert, undated (Box 6)
      - Ingwersen, Paul, undated (Box 6)
      - Ireland, Doug, undated (Box 6)
      - Irwin, Mark, undated (Box 6)
      - Irwin, William H., undated (Box 6)
      - Jaffe, Michelle, undated (Box 6)
      - Jet Propulsion Laboratory, undated (Box 6)
      - Johns, Josef, undated (Box 6)
      - Jones, Robert, undated (Box 6)
      - Joseph, Larry, undated (Box 6)
      - Kallunki, Jacquelyn, undated (Box 6)
      - Kalstone, David, undated (Box 6)
      - Kane, Paul, undated (Box 6)
      - Kaplan, Martha, undated (Box 6)
      - Karpeles, Eric, undated; 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Kaufman, David, undated (Box 6)
      - Kelaidis, Panayoti, undated (Box 6)
      - Kennedy, Brandon, undated (Box 6)
      - Kennedy, Robert F., undated (Box 6)
      - Kenney, Richard, undated (Box 6)
      - Kermani, David, undated (Box 6)
      - Kernan, Nathan, undated; 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Killian, Kevin, undated (Box 6)
      - Killian, Sean, undated (Box 6)
      - Kinzie, Mary, undated (Box 6)
      - Kirchwey, Karl, undated (Box 6)
      - Kirkbride, Joseph, undated (Box 6)
      - Kleinzahler, August, undated (Box 6)
      - Koenig, Steven, undated (Box 6)
      - Koestenbaum, Wayne, undated (Box 6)
      - Koethe, John, undated; 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Kolovakos, Gregory, undated (Box 7)
      - Koniecko, Scott, undated (Box 7)
      - Konigsberg, Laura, undated (Box 7)
      - Kotarski, Bev (Rzeszutko), undated (Box 7)
      - Kozloff, Max, undated (Box 7)
      - Krieger, Martin, undated (Box 7)
      - Krueger, Mary, undated (Box 7)
      - Kudlacek, Martina, undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Kurshan, Ilana, undated (Box 7)
      - Laird, Susan, undated (Box 7)
      - Laurans, Penelope, undated (Box 7)
      - Lauterbach, Ann, undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Leake, Eugene, undated (Box 7)
      - Leaska, Mitchell, undated (Box 7)
      - Leavy, Dennis, undated (Box 7)
      - Lehman, David, undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Leibowitz, Herb, undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Lemon, Alan, undated (Box 7)
      - Lentz, Sue, undated (Box 7)
      - Lerner, Michael, undated (Box 7)
      - Leslie, Alfred, undated (Box 7)
      - Levin, Phillis, undated (Box 7)
      - Levin, Sander M., undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Levitte, Jean-David, undated (Box 7)
      - Levy, Ellen, undated (Box 7)
      - Lewis, Leon, undated (Box 7)
      - Lewis, Zina (Stetler), undated (Box 7)
      - Lin, Robert, undated (Box 7)
      - Link, Arthur S., undated (Box 7)
      - Lipe, Clark and Gordon Bocox, undated (Box 7)
      - Lippy, Tod, undated (Box 7)
      - Liston, Aaron, undated (Box 7)
      - Little, Brown, undated (Box 7)
      - Little, John E., undated (Box 7)
      - Liu, Timothy, undated (Box 7)
      - Livadas, Dorothy, undated (Box 7)
      - Lockard, Duane, undated (Box 7)
      - Logerquist, Allen, undated (Box 7)
      - Long, Charles Robert, undated (Box 7)
      - Long, Marie, undated (Box 7)
      - Longenbach, James, undated (Box 7)
      - Lopate, Phillip, undated (Box 7)
      - Lubin, Moshe, undated (Box 7)
      - Lyman, Lester, undated (Box 7)
      - MacArthur, Marit (Joanie), undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Maddock, Jerome, undated (Box 7)
      - Magid, Nora, undated (Box 7)
      - Mahon, Terrence, undated (Box 7)
      - Malanga, Gerard, undated (Box 7)
      - Malina, Judith, undated (Box 7)
      - Maloney, Dennis, undated (Box 7)
      - Manno, Joe, undated (Box 7)
      - March on Washington, undated (Box 7)
      - Margaronis, Maria, undated (Box 7)
      - Marshall, Melissa, undated (Box 7)
      - Martin, Richard, undated (Box 7)
      - Mathews, Harry, undated (Box 7)
      - McAlvey, Anne (Crase), undated (Box 7)
      - McCaffrey, Joseph, undated (Box 7)
      - McClatchy, J.D., undated (Box 7)
      - McCorkle, James, undated (Box 7)
      - McCullough, Frances, undated (Box 7)
      - McDermontt, Keith, undated (Box 7)
      - McFall, Gardner, undated (Box 7)
      - McGrath, Charles, undated (Box 7)
      - McLaren, Marilyn, undated (Box 7)
      - McNabb, Gerry, undated (Box 7)
      - McQuilkin, Rob, undated (Box 7)
      - McWilliams, Carey, undated (Box 7)
      - Mekas, Jonas, undated (Box 7)
      - Menchaca, Frank, undated (Box 7)
      - Merla, Patrick, undated (Box 7)
      - Merill, Christopher, undated (Box 7)
      - Merill, James, undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
        Including For James Merill: A Birthday Tribute, assembled by McClatchy for Merill's sixtieth birthday in 1986, with poem by Douglas. A thank you inscribed from Merrill in Eight Bits (folded sheet in wrappers) is laid in.
      - Messologhites, Louisa, undated (Box 7)
      - Meyer, Steven, undated (Box 8)
      - Michener, Christian, undated (Box 8)
      - Michigan Grad School, undated (Box 8)
      - Michigan Law School, undated (Box 8)
      - Mintz, Ward, undated (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 8)
      - Moore, Harold, undated (Box 8)
      - Moore, Honor, undated (Box 8)
      - More, Michael, undated (Box 8)
      - Morrison, Madison, undated (Box 8)
      - Morrissette, Michaela, undated (Box 8)
      - Morse, Carl, undated (Box 8)
      - Moss, Christoph, undated (Box 8)
      - Moss, Howard, undated (Box 8)
      - Motika, Stephen, undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Moye, William, undated (Box 8)
      - Myers, John Bernard, undated (Box 8)
      - Myers, L. Budd, undated (Box 8)
      - Myles, Eileen, undated (Box 8)
      - Nabut, Martin (LLE), undated (Box 8)
      - Nadel, Kenneth, undated (Box 8)
      - National Book Critics Circle, undated (Box 8)
      - Naylor, Charles, undated (Box 8)
      - Nazarene, Robert, undated (Box 8)
      - Nee, Michael, undated (Box 8)
      - Nelson, Gladys, undated (Box 8)
      - Nelson, Janet, undated (Box 8)
      - NYU, undated (Box 8)
      - Niedecker Committee, undated (Box 8)
      - Nichols, Jeff, undated (Box 8)
      - Nichols, Sarah, undated (Box 8)
      - Nix, James, undated (Box 8)
      - Nims, John Frederick, undated (Box 8)
      - Noguere, Suzanne, undated (Box 8)
      - North, Charles, undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
      - O'Keefe, Michael, undated (Box 8)
      - Olsen, Scott, undated (Box 8)
      - O'Meara, John, undated (Box 8)
      - O'Rourke, Meghan, undated (Box 8)
      - Oppenheim, Thomas, undated (Box 8)
      - Osbourne, Ralph, undated (Box 8)
      - Padgett, Ron, undated (Box 8)
      - Pagels, Heinz, undated (Box 8)
      - Parini, Jay, undated (Box 8)
      - Parisi, Joseph, undated (Box 8)
      - Park, Darragh, undated (Box 8)
      - Parker, Harold R., undated (Box 8)
      - Parlatore, Anselm, undated (Box 8)
      - Paschen, Elise, undated (Box 8)
      - Pellitteri, Sal, undated (Box 8)
      - Penberthy, Jenny, undated (Box 8)
      - People Against Racism, undated (Box 8)
      - Perl, Jed, undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Perloff, Marjorie, undated (Box 8)
      - Perl-Rosenthal, Nathan and Jessica Marglin, undated (Box 8)
      - Permissions for Both, undated (Box 8)
      - Petruzelli, David, undated (Box 8)
      - Pettet, Simon, undated (Box 8)
      - Pierce, Edward, undated (Box 8)
      - Pike, Mary, undated (Box 8)
      - Pincoe, Elaine [née Fabinski], undated (Box 8)
      - Pinkava, Donald, undated (Box 8)
      - Pinsky, Robert, undated (Box 8)
      - Plohn, Charles, undated (Box 8)
      - Pochoda, Elizabeth, undated (Box 8)
      - Poirier, Richard, undated (Box 8)
      - Polach, Frank, undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Political Reform Commission of the Michigan Democratic Party, undated (Box 8)
      - Polito, Robert, undated (Box 8)
      - Porter, Anne, undated (Box 8)
      - Poulin, Al, undated (Box 8)
      - Pouls, M.A., undated (Box 8)
      - Power, Phillip, undated (Box 8)
      - Preston, Stuart, undated (Box 8)
      - Project Talent, undated (Box 8)
      - Pruitt, Keith, undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Pujat, Duressa (Ridgway), undated (Box 8)
      - Puiniello, Francoise, undated (Box 8)
      - Pursglove, Glyn, undated (Box 8)
      - Quaintance, Don, undated (Box 9)
      - Quilter, Jenni, undated (Box 9)
      - Quinn, Alice, undated (Box 9)
      - Rabinowitz, Johnathan, undated (Box 9)
      - Radomsky, Rosalie, undated (Box 9)
      - Rawlins, Scott, undated (Box 9)
      - Raworth, Tom, undated (Box 9)
      - Realtors, undated (Box 9)
      - Rector, Liam, undated (Box 9)
      - Reiff, Andy, undated (Box 9)
      - Reisem ,Richard, undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Rejections, undated (Box 9)
      - Reveal, James, undated (Box 9)
      - Revell, Donald, undated (Box 9)
      - Reynolds, Ann, undated (Box 9)
      - Richie, Eugene, undated (Box 9)
      - Rieger, James, undated (Box 9)
      - Rippon, John, undated (Box 9)
      - Robinson, Susan, undated (Box 9)
      - Rochester, undated (Box 9)
      - Rolfe, Susan (Polach), undated (Box 9)
      - Rood-Sinker, Sabrina, undated (Box 9)
      - Rorem, Ned, undated (Box 9)
      - Rose, Stephanie, undated (Box 9)
      - Rosen, Michael, undated (Box 9)
      - Rosenberg, Tina, undated (Box 9)
      - Rosenheim, Kellye, undated (Box 9)
      - Rosenthal, Deborah, undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Rosenthal, Joel, undated (Box 9)
      - Roub, Gail, undated (Box 9)
      - Rudell, Jeffery, undated (Box 9)
      - Rutherford, Albert G., undated (Box 9)
      - Runyon, Joy, undated (Box 9)
      - Sabel, Hanna, undated (Box 9)
      - Saralegui, Alejandro, undated (Box 9)
      - Sarasson, Jeffrey, undated (Box 9)
      - Scharrer, Gary, undated (Box 9)
      - Schiavo, Michael, undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Schilbilsky, Michael, undated (Box 9)
      - Schleger, Peter, undated (Box 9)
      - Schmall, Jeremy, undated (Box 9)
      - Schmid, Rudolf, undated (Box 9)
      - Schmidt, Michael, undated (Box 9)
      - Schneier [Edward], undated (Box 9)
      - Schreiber, Steve, undated (Box 9)